{
  "title": "Financial and bank expressions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Can you please ........ some money until we get paid next week?",
      "answers": ["lend", "give", "borrow", "grant"],
      "correct": "lend"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "I decided to invest in the commodities market as the ...... .. on offer from bank was at an all time low.",
      "answers": ["increase", "interest", "rent", "tax"],
      "correct": "interest"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Many retailers in Jakarta refuse to exchange purchases unless you can show them/ our ........",
      "answers": ["recipe", "receipt", "bill", "change"],
      "correct": "receipt"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "My boss informed me that I had been nominated to ........ a sales pitch to one of our company's largest buyers ",
      "answers": ["make", "perform", "talk", "do"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I saw a very good ........ advertised in the newspaper this week.",
      "answers": ["employment", "occupation", "work", "job"],
      "correct": "job"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "My wife has a ........ job at the department store.",
      "answers": ["half-time", "spare-time", "part-time", "over-time"],
      "correct": "part-time"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The psychiatrist gave his patient a ........ for some medicine. ",
      "answers": ["recipe", "statement", "prescription", "receipt"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "When a fire broke out at the Louvre, at least twenty ........ paintings were destroyed including two by Henri Matisse.",
      "answers": ["worthless", "priceless", "valueless", "useless"],
      "correct": "priceless"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "I must remember to fill in my tax ........ before the end of this week.",
      "answers": ["return", "declaration", "brochure", "pamphlet"],
      "correct": "return"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Can you take this money to the bank and make a ........ for me? ",
      "answers": ["loan", "transaction", "deposit", "withdrawal"],
      "correct": "deposit"
    }
  ]
}
